Second interview.
I have a main project, and I would like to ask you to make a cute title call for it!
Yes, my three-piece element
Now, I would like to ask you to announce what are the three elements that make up this Ritsuki-san.
Here we go!
Let's see, let's see!
Yes, the first one, fantasy.
The first, words.
The third, comedy.
The third one, comedy
(Ending theme)
The first one
Fantasia
Yes, I am a magical girl
Yes, I've heard about you.
Is it true?
Yes, from what I've heard.
Yes, I'm a magical girl.
I like that kind of...
I like fairy tale worlds.
That's why I'm here in the human world.
It's true, it's true, it's true.
That's how I used to be.
Well, no, no, I don't dislike it at all.
It's just...
That's it? Well...
The shape and form are exactly the same in the human world.
Fantasy
That's right.
Magical world
Yes, sir.
Oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And then, you know, it's almost like it's, you know...
I mean, you're from that world.
Yes, I do.
Well, how long have you been here?
Well, 21 years.
Oh, I see. So you've been here since birth.
Yes, that's right.
Well, how is it really? How do you feel about the human world these days?
I'm trying to push myself, but...
Oh, is that you?
Or is it the people who are already looking around here?
I am.
I'm pushing myself.
The fact that I can't go over here much...
I don't know which it is.
That's great. That's great.
I don't know about this.
No, but I can't tell if you're giving me the warm shoulder here or the don't-touch-me-anymore look.
I can't tell if they're giving me a warm look or a "don't touch me anymore" look.
I just can't get over how much I love this little tingly love triangle.
I'm sorry, I don't know which one you're talking about.
But it's so true.
You're involved in a lot of group activities, aren't you?
In the form of Mr. Zombie.
Do you have a fantasy member who is close to me?
Do you have any?
Fantasy member? Fantasy member?
I'm the only one whose face has clouded over today.
What? But who do you think is most like you?
Miyu Fujitani.
Oh, really?
Fantasy.
Fantasy... I think she's the most like me.
I see.
It's something I hold very dear to my heart.
Yes.
This program is...
So many things...
Shou-chan, who's been interested in Runchan lately
Shirikon-san
Kazuma-san
Mr. Okuda provided this program.
Thank you very much!
Chippewa